http://www.geworkersunited.org/privacy-policy/

IUE-CWA GE Members, Using your cell phone, text the word GE to 69866 to sign up for text message updates on the National GE Bargaining.
GE News
Why Union?
Take Action!
CBC Unions
Meet the Leaders
IUE-CWA President Carl Kennebrew, Chairman of the GE-CBC
Jerry Carney, IUE-CWA Conference Board Chairman and CBC Lead Negotiator
Privacy Policy
Effective Oct 1, 2014
IUE-CWA respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how IUE-CWA uses the personal information we collect through the GE Workers United website (the “Website”).  By using or accessing the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected online through the Website and does not describe the ways in which we may collect or use information obtained offline or through any means other than our Website. IUE-CWA may modify this policy from time to time so we encourage you to check this page when revisiting this website. The type and amount of information received depends on how you use the site.
Website Usage/Information Collection
When you visit the Website, we automatically obtain information from you about the name of your Internet service provider, the browser and type of computer you are using, the website that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time of those requests. We use this information on an aggregate basis to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors. For example, we use this information to track which pages are most popular among visitors as a whole.  We may record information about your usage of the Website, such as when you use the site, the areas of the site you click on and/or participate in, the tags you search for, and whether or not you subscribe to the RSS feed. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. A persistent cookie may be used to track this information. We may use pixel tags and/or trackable links in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and/or clicked on by recipients.  We do not collect or store personally identifiable information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address or phone number, unless you provide that information.
Collection of Personally Identifiable Information
IUE-CWA provides web forms so you may provide your contact information to engage in IUE-CWA activities such as online activism (i.e., contact Congress), to place orders for products or services or to correspond with IUE-CWA. Any information we collect, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, type of request you are making and any additional information you provide, is collected and stored by IUE-CWA. The information is used to fulfill your request, to engage you and your co-workers in advocacy and activism, and track aggregate information about usage of these features. IUE-CWA makes every effort to ensure the secure collection and transmission of your sensitive information using industry accepted data collection and encryption methodologies, such as SSL (Secure Sockets Layer).
SPECIAL NOTICE FOR PARENTS
IUE-CWA does not knowingly collect, use or distribute children’s personally identifiable information to any third parties. We want to help you guard your children’s privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet. When using our apps or websites, please do not enter names, ages, or other personal information of individuals under age 14. If you have any reservations, questions or concerns about your child’s access to this site or how information that your child provides is used by us, please contact us.
IUE-CWA’s Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information
IUE-CWA may share personal information you give us with other labor organizations if we believe you would be interested in receiving communications from these organizations, for example, the AFL-CIO, Union Privilege, or a Local Union, as well as third parties that perform services on our behalf. These third party providers are committed to protecting the privacy of our members and subscribers, and will not utilize your information for any other purpose but to provide the services which we contract for.
The Website will not post your personal contact information, including e-mail address, street address and phone numbers, without your consent. Without such consent, website staff will withhold posting personal contact information for that individual.
Financial Information and Payments
We use a secure server for processing payments and financial information.. IUE-CWA staff retrieves the encrypted information from the secure site and transmits it to the bank via the software that the bank provides for this purpose. IUE-CWA does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. The Website uses a cookie for measuring aggregate web statistics, including number of monthly visitors, number of repeat visitors, most popular Web pages and other information. IUE-CWA will also use cookies to facilitate your online visit by maintaining data that you provide for online activism activities so that you will not need to resubmit certain information.
Geolocation Data
If you choose to provide location data via a location-based service feature on our website, we may collect and use location data as you provide, or as sent from your device, to provide and improve location-based products and services.
Opting Out of E-mail Lists
People who subscribe to e-mail lists via the website will receive periodic updates from IUE-CWA by regular mail, fax or e-mail. You may opt out of receiving future information via e-mail by using the unsubscribe procedure specified on the e-mail message.
Outside Links
This site contains hypertext links to other sites. IUE-CWA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security
IUE-CWA takes security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
If you send us an e-mail, you should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. So, if your communication includes sensitive information like your bank account, charge card, or social security number, and you prefer not to use one of our secure online complaint forms, contact us by mail or by telephone rather than by e-mail.
Corrections/Updating Personal Information
If your personal information changes (such as your ZIP code), or if you wish to have your information removed from our database, contact us and we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that personal data provided to us.
Contact Us
If you experience technical problems with the operation of this web site, contact us.
Terms of Service
User Agreement
Welcome to the IUE-CWA Website. Please carefully review our User Agreement before you begin using the site. Thank you.
Your Acceptance
Welcome to IUE-CWA.org. By using and/or visiting this Website, you signify your agreement to (1) these terms and conditions (the “User Agreement”), (2) IUE-CWA’s Privacy Policy, incorporated here by reference, and (3) IUE-CWA’s Community Guidelines, also incorporated here by reference. If you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions contained in this User Agreement, the Privacy Policy, or Community Guidelines, you are not authorized to use the Website.
Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this User Agreement, you should periodically review the most up-to-date version. IUE-CWA may, in its sole discretion, modify this User Agreement at any time. By continuing to use this website following our posting of such changes, you agree to be bound by this User Agreement, as modified.
Through our sites, IUE-CWA provides users with access to a rich array of educational resources, including personalized content. We hope you find our sites useful. We reserve the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue the Website or any related sites, or any part of them, at any time, for any reason without prior notice to you. You agree that we shall not be liable for any such modification, suspension, or discontinuance.
Your registration information, as well as other personally identifiable information that you provide us about yourself on our sites, is subject to our Privacy Policy. Click here to read our Privacy Policy.
General Use of the Website — Permissions and Restrictions
IUE-CWA hereby grants you permission to access and use the Website as set forth in this User Agreement, provided that:
You do not collect any personally identifiable information of others, including user names or email addresses, from the Website.
You do not use the Website for any commercial purposes without the prior written authorization of IUE-CWA. You agree not to transmit or otherwise make available any unsolicited advertising, promotional information, bulk e-mail or other solicitation. You agree not to solicit, for commercial purposes, any users of the Website with respect to material they post on the Website.
You do not use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, “robots,” “spiders,” or “offline readers,” that accesses the Website in a manner that sends more request messages to the IUE-CWA servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional online web browser. Notwithstanding the foregoing, IUE-CWA grants the operators of public search engines permission to use spiders to copy materials from the site for the sole purpose of and solely to the extent necessary for creating publicly available searchable indices of the materials, but not caches or archives of such materials. IUE-CWA reserves the right to revoke these exceptions either generally or in specific cases.
You do not transmit or otherwise make available any content containing any “virus,” “worm,” “trojan horse,” or any other computer code, file, or program designed to interrupt, destroy, or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment.
You do not alter or modify any part of the Website.
You do not circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the Website or our sites or servers (or networks connected to our Website).
You do not harass, threaten, embarrass, or cause distress, unwanted attention, or discomfort to a person or entity on or through the Website or its communication systems.
You do not transmit or otherwise make available on or through the Website any content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, hateful, or racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable, as solely determined by IUE-CWA.
IUE-CWA reserves the right to change or discontinue any aspect of the Website at any time, for any reason, and without notice to you.
IUE-CWA reserves the right to suspend or terminate a user’s access to the Website, without prior notice and at IUE-CWA’s sole discretion.
This list of permissions and restrictions, along with the other terms discussed below, is not intended to be complete, but merely illustrative. We reserve the right in our sole and final judgment to determine whether conduct violates conduct requirements for the Website.
IUE-CWA Registered User Accounts
In order to access some features of the Website, such as, for example, interactive blogs, you have to become a Registered User, which will also create a user account. As a Registered User, you agree to be bound by the following terms:
When creating or modifying your account, you must provide accurate, current, and complete information. We reserve the right to disallow use of any user name that we deem offensive or inappropriate. You will be responsible for preserving the confidentiality of your password and for all actions of persons accessing the Website through any username/password assigned to you. You must notify IUE-CWA immediately of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account. You may never use another’s account without permission.
As a Registered User you may submit comments on various IUE-CWA blogs or other material (collectively, “User Content”) to the Website. IUE-CWA reserves the right, but does not assume the obligation, to delete, move, condense, or edit such User Content for any reason and without prior notice. IUE-CWA also reserves the right to suspend or terminate a Registered User’s access for posting User Content.
You are solely responsible for your own User Content and the consequences of posting or publishing it. You affirm, represent, and/or warrant that: you own, or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions to use and authorize IUE-CWA to use, all patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights in and to all User Content you submit to enable inclusion and use of such User Content in the manner contemplated by the Website and these Terms of Service.
You retain all of your ownership rights in your User Content. However, by submitting User Content to IUE-CWA, you hereby grant IUE-CWA a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicenseable, perpetual, and transferable license to use, reproduce, store, distribute, prepare derivative works of and display your User Content (and your user name) in any medium in connection with the activities and operations of IUE-CWA, its affiliated entities and successors. You also hereby grant each user of the Website a non-exclusive license to access your User Content through the Website, and to use, reproduce, and distribute such User Content for such user’s personal, non-commercial purposes. You understand and agree that IUE-CWA may retain, reproduce, distribute and otherwise use for any purpose copies of User Content that has been removed from the Website. The above licenses granted by you are perpetual and irrevocable.
IUE-CWA does not endorse, authorize or ratify any User Content, or any opinion, recommendation, or advice expressed therein, and IUE-CWA expressly disclaims all liability in connection with User Content. IUE-CWA does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights on its Website, and IUE-CWA reserves the right, but does not assume the obligation, to remove any content from the Website if notified that such content infringes on another’s intellectual property rights.
Your Use of Content on the Site
In addition to the restrictions above, the following restrictions and conditions apply specifically to your use of content on the Website.
The content on the Website (other than your User Content), including without limitation, the text, software, scripts, graphics, photos, sounds, music, videos, interactive features and the like (collectively, “IUE-CWA Content”) is owned by or licensed by IUE-CWA. Similarly, the trademarks, service marks and logos contained on the Website are owned or licensed by IUE-CWA (“IUE-CWA Marks”). Except as otherwise provided in this User Agreement or elsewhere on the website (e.g., in the description of a campaign), the IUE-CWA Content and the IUE-CWA Marks may not be downloaded, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any purpose whatsoever without the prior written consent of IUE-CWA. IUE-CWA reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the IUE-CWA Content and the IUE-CWA Marks.
The Website is made available for your personal, non-commercial use only. As part of such use, you may display, download and/or print pages from the site; you may link to the Website; and you may forward Website materials to others for personal, non-commercial uses that are reasonably related to the Website’s purposes.
You understand that when using the Website, you will be exposed to IUE-CWA Content, User Content, and other third-party content from a variety of sources, and that IUE-CWA makes no warranty about the accuracy, usefulness, safety, or intellectual property rights of or relating to such IUE-CWA Content, User Content, or other third-party content. You further understand and acknowledge that you may be exposed to User Content that may be inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable, and you agree to waive, and hereby do waive, any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against IUE-CWA with respect thereto.
The Website may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by IUE-CWA. IUE-CWA has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each other website that you visit.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act
If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any IUE-CWA Content or User Content infringes upon your copyright, you may submit a notification pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) by providing IUE-CWA’s Copyright Agent with the following information in writing (see 17 U.S.C 512(c)(3) for further detail):
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed;
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit IUE-CWA to locate the material;
A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are, or are authorized to act on behalf of, the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address; and
A physical or electronic signature of the owner of the exclusive right that is allegedly infringed, or that of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner.
IUE-CWA’s designated Copyright Agent to receive notifications of claimed infringement can be reached at copyright@IUE-CWA.org. You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the above requirements, your DMCA notice may not be valid.
For clarity, only DMCA notices should go to the Copyright Agent. Please use the Contact Us form for any other feedback, comments, requests for technical support, or other communications with IUE-CWA.
Warranty Disclaimer
THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU “AS IS.” YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE IUE-CWA WEBSITE SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IUE-CWA, AS WELL AS ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS (COLLECTIVELY, THE “IUE-CWA PARTIES”), DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, IN CONNECTION WITH THE WEBSITE AND YOUR USE THEREOF. THE IUE-CWA PARTIES CANNOT AND DO NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, CURRENTNESS, NONINFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OF THE SITE’S CONTENT OR THE CONTENT OF ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE. NOR DO THE IUE-CWA PARTIES GUARANTEE THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE ERROR FREE, OR CONTINUOUSLY AVAILABLE, OR THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. THE IUE-CWA PARTIES DO NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE PROVIDED, ADVERTISED OR OFFERED BY A THIRD PARTY THROUGH THE IUE-CWA WEBSITE OR ANY HYPERLINKED WEBSITE OR FEATURED IN ANY BANNER OR OTHER ADVERTISING.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE IUE-CWA PARTIES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, WHETHER OR NOT THEY ARE FORESEEABLE, RELATING TO THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING ANY DAMAGES RESULTING FROM ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE, (III) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR WEBSITE, (V) BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE, WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR WEBSITE BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (VI) ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE IUE-CWA WEBSITE, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT IUE-CWA IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE IUE-CWA PARTIES SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR USER CONTENT OR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE, OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY AND THAT THE RISK OF HARM OR DAMAGE FROM THE FOREGOING RESTS ENTIRELY WITH YOU. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. TO THE EXTENT THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OF THE PROVISIONS SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT MAY NOT APPLY. YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS THE IUE-CWA PARTIES AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, OF WHATEVER NATURE, THAT ARISE OUT OF YOUR USE OF AND ACCESS TO THE IUE-CWA WEBSITE OR YOUR VIOLATION OF ANY OF THIS USER AGREEMENT. THIS INDEMNIFICATION OBLIGATION WILL SURVIVE THIS USER AGREEMENT AND YOUR USE OF THE IUE-CWA WEBSITE.
Ability to Accept User Agreement
You affirm that you are either more than 18 years of age, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this User Agreement, and to abide by and comply with this User Agreement. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as the IUE-CWA Website is not intended for children under 13.
Miscellaneous
This User Agreement shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of Washington, D.C., without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Any claim or dispute between you and IUE-CWA that arises in whole or in part from the Website shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Washington, D.C. This User Agreement, together with the Privacy Policy and any other legal notices published by IUE-CWA on the Website, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and IUE-CWA concerning the Website and supersedes prior agreements, if any, between you and IUE-CWA relating to any matter dealt with in the User Agreement. If any provision of this User Agreement is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this User Agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this User Agreement shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and IUE-CWA’s failure to assert any right or provision under this User Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. This User Agreement, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred or assigned by you, but may be assigned by IUE-CWA without restriction. This User Agreement and the rights and obligations created hereunder shall be binding upon and inure solely to the benefits of the parties hereto and their respective successors and assigns, and nothing in this Agreement, express or implied, is intended or should be construed to confer upon any other person any right, remedy or claim under or by virtue of this Agreement.
You and IUE-CWA agree that any cause of action arising out of or related to the Website must commence within one (1) year after the cause of action accrues. Otherwise, such cause of action is permanently barred.
This User Agreement is made effective as of Oct 1, 2014.
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
© 2020
IUE-CWA
